<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[EATSLEEPREPEAT.NET]]></title>
  <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/"/>
  <updated>2012-10-13T15:32:15+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Matt Silverlock]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[matt@eatsleeprepeat.net]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[York]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/york/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-13T12:01:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/york</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Left home at 4:30AM to make it here by sunrise, to instead be greeted by overcast skies. We made the most of the morning anyway, exploring quiet lots and empty roads alike. It&#8217;s not bad for a quaint country town just 1.5 hours out of Perth.</p>

<p><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0478-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Field" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0486-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Wreck" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0495-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Pump" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0498-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Ford" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0500-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Weir" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuji X100 - Three Months In]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/fuji-x100-three-months-in/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-04T08:07:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/fuji-x100-three-months-in</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;ve had the <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0043RS864/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=eatsleeprepea-20">X100</a> for three months now, and I feel it&#8217;s time to add a few things to my <a href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/fuji-x100-review/">original review</a>. This review will be a little more technical than the first, but there (still) won&#8217;t be any pixel peeping here.</p>

<p>First up: the RAW files. They&#8217;re great, and there&#8217;s a <em>lot</em> of latitude in them. I pushed a bunch of files from the <a href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/say-anything/">Say Anything</a> gig I went to—which I shot at ISO3200—a minimum of one stop and saw very little chroma (colour) noise. What noise there was had a great &#8220;film&#8221; look, and pushing the files around with my usual Lightroom + Photoshop + Alien Skin Exposure workflow didn&#8217;t cause any problems. I&#8217;m still comfortably leaving the X100 set to ISO800/1000 on a daily basis (and using the ND filter to control shutter speed), without the need to worry about dull colours or ugly/distracting noise.</p>

<p>The battery life has been rock solid. There are some who seem to believe it has a sub-par battery life—and I guess if you&#8217;re coming from an pro-grade DSLR, then it may seem bad in comparison—but it manages weeks on standby with a good handful of shots in-between. It also coped with four days away when I went to <a href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/yallingup/">Yallingup</a> in July—the spare batteries I brought down with me never saw any use (it was still near-full almost a week later). It might be the fact that I review sparingly and spend most of my time using the OVF that contributes to this—I&#8217;m not the kind to &#8220;spray and pray&#8221;.</p>

<p>Reliability-wise, it hasn&#8217;t locked up once. I&#8217;ve had firmware v1.30 on it since day zero, so that may have something to do with it, but I&#8217;ve never had to pop the battery out to reset the camera. It&#8217;s almost managed to avoid any real dings or scratches, despite living sans-case in an inside pocket of my messenger bag. I have a JJC filter adapter ring and a <a href="http://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/622143-REG/B_W_66_042015_66_042015_49mm_Digital_Pro.html">silver B+W UV filter</a> on it; I don&#8217;t use the hood as it adds too much depth. I not usually one to run with a UV filter on my cameras, but the X100 is the exception: it&#8217;s an every-day, always-there tool, and any damage to the lens means the whole camera is out of action. I just made sure to buy a decent filter to minimise any added ghosting or flare, and so far I haven&#8217;t had any problems.</p>

<p>The LCD could probably be a bit better (higher-res), and I have started to bump the AF mode dial on the front a bit more than I&#8217;d like. Part of that is attributed to the fact that it lives in my messenger bag (sans-case) and/or the cup-holder in my car, and therefore is outright more prone to being knocked. I&#8217;ve gotten used to the rear dial, but it&#8217;s still a bit fiddly. Can&#8217;t do much about that though—and it doesn&#8217;t hugely impact the usability of the camera.</p>

<p>The <a href="http://www.gordyscamerastraps.com/neck-string-double/index.htm">Gordy&#8217;s</a> strap (string; double attach; 50&#8221;) that I picked up for it is still going strong, too. Matches the X100 well and is just long enough to sling bandolier-style over my body—but long enough that I can still pull the viewfinder up to my eye comfortably.</p>

<p>I&#8217;m still loving the OVF—even more as time goes on. I&#8217;m forever liking the frame-lines and what is effectively &#8220;greater than 100%&#8221; frame coverage. I do occasionally flick it over to the EVF if I really need to nail a composition—or shoot something close—but the other 90% of the time I&#8217;m using the OVF. It takes maybe a week to get used to the accuracy of the frame-lines vs. the distance of what you&#8217;re shooting (and therefore your composition)—but after that it&#8217;s smooth sailing.</p>

<p>The more time I spend with the X100 the more I know I made the right choice. There&#8217;s no buyer&#8217;s remorse here, despite considering the NEX-7 (unexciting RAW files; expensive with the 24mm), OM-D (too SLR-like), and the X-Pro 1 (just that bit too big). I can comfortably &#8220;see&#8221; in 35mm, which means I can almost frame a shot before lifting the camera to my eye. It&#8217;s never intrusive at dinner tables, in the car, or over my shoulder on long walks. It rarely struggles in less-than-ideal lighting, excels in good light, and gives me the control I want; all of these things are exactly what I was after. It&#8217;s almost a shame I waited so long to buy one.</p>

<p><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0173-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="ISO 1000, f/2, 1/120s" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2012 Perth Royal Show]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/2012-perth-royal-show/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-02T07:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/2012-perth-royal-show</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Just a small batch this year, including a re-take of my old favorite (the Python Loop). We went late in the day and enjoyed hot cinnamon donuts, hot dogs and bratwurst.</p>

<p><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0473-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Superbowl" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0459-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Chair Lift" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0471-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Loop Redux" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[iPhone 5 Wallpapers]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/iphone-5-wallpapers/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-25T08:53:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/iphone-5-wallpapers</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>First up: sorry for the slow updates. It&#8217;s been a busy couple of months. Saying that, I do have a trips to the Perth Royal Show, York &amp; New Norcia planned over the next couple of weeks, so expect more photos soon.</p>

<p>I also bought an iPhone 5 yesterday and recognised a dearth of usable wallpapers (1136px x 640px). I&#8217;ve since corrected that. You can grab this pack of four <a href="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/iphone5_wallpapers_20120925.zip">here</a>. I may go through my archives and add a few more, too.</p>

<p><a href="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/iphone5_wallpapers_20120925.zip"><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/iphone5_wallpapers_strip_20120925.jpg" alt="iPhone 5 Wallpapers" /></a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waffling On]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/waffling-on/"/>
    <updated>2012-08-05T08:12:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/waffling-on</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Discovered a neat little waffle place called <a href="http://www.urbanspoon.com/r/338/1686816/restaurant/Perth/Superstar-Waffles-Northbridge">Superstar Waffles</a> here in Northbridge. Had a latte (good!) and shared a few bites from a waffle-on-a-stick with condensed milk (great!). I&#8217;m definitely a fan.</p>

<p>The store itself is very minimalist, from the iPad-as-the-till down to the spartan tables and chairs. It&#8217;s cozy, too, so plan to avoid usual busy periods or get something to go.</p>

<p><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0436-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Machines" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0437-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Coffee" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0438-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Waffles" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0439-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Opening Hours" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Yallingup]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/yallingup/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-29T17:15:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/yallingup</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Decided we needed a weekend away after a busy first half of the year after balancing moving, study and work. We stayed at Yallingup Beach Holiday Park—Em&#8217;s favorite spot down in Yallingup—for three nights. It&#8217;s also 50m from the beach, which is just about as close as you can get without being in the ocean. Waking up to the crashing of waves was always a good way to start the day.</p>

<p>What did we get up to? In no particular order, we walked along the beach, took a few photos, ate cheese kranksy&#8217;s and hash browns, devoured the fruit bread and sourdough from the <a href="http://www.urbanspoon.com/r/348/1542382/restaurant/Western-Australia/Yallingup-Woodfired-Bakery-Dunsborough">Yallingup Woodfired Bakery</a>, and went for a quick drive in the winter cold to shoot some stars.</p>

<p>Not bad for two-and-a-half hours from Perth.</p>

<p><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0371-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Rock" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0376-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Breakfast" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0395-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Beach" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0398-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Overgrowth" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0418-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Moss" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0382-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Bread" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0412-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Dusk" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0416-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Outward" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0429-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Stars" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Say Anything]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/say-anything/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-12T07:03:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/say-anything</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Fantastic gig. Max Bemis has incredible stage presence. Shot this at ISO3200 on the X100 as I jostled around up front.</p>

<p><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0354-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Max Bemis" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0348-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="On Stage" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0337-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Posters" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazy Sundays]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/lazy-sundays/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-08T16:47:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/lazy-sundays</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Just two quick ones before the week ends.</p>

<p><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0313-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Vines" />
<img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0322-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="Em with her Instax" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuji X100 Review]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/fuji-x100-review/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-08T12:54:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/fuji-x100-review</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>First up: this isn&#8217;t a technical, pixel peeping review—it is however a review about the user experience, handling and image character. If that floats your boat, read on.</p>

<p>So: I bought a <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0043RS864/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=eatsleeprepea-20&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=390957&amp;creativeASIN=B0043RS864">Fuji X100</a> three weeks ago to replace my Panasonic GF1 + 20mm kit, which originally &#8220;replaced&#8221; my 5D Mark II + 35L. I was no longer worried about chasing paid work, and was instead just shooting street, editorial and landscapes for (mostly) myself. Having a camera that I could take <em>everywhere</em> (i.e. didn&#8217;t need its own bag) was a huge driving factor in getting the GF1, even if overall image quality wasn&#8217;t the same. It really didn&#8217;t matter though, and I ended up taking a ton of great photos with it. It did have its quirks—average AF, dynamic range/RAW files, and no viewfinder—but those were trade-offs I was willing to make. When the X100 came out, I wasn&#8217;t totally sold: I didn&#8217;t really read up on it and my GF1 wasn&#8217;t bugging me too much, so I keep shooting with what I had. But I kept running across amazing images from the X100, and the so-so RAW files from the GF1 (esp. compared with my old 5D2) were starting to grate just a little.</p>

<p>I sold my GF1 and lenses (I also had the 45mm f2.8 macro), waited for someone local to get stock, and bought the X100. And so far it&#8217;s been outstanding.</p>

<p>The optical viewfinder (OVF), first of all, rocks. It&#8217;s big, it&#8217;s clear, and the best part about it is that it covers <em>beyond</em> the frame, allowing you to spot people just outside your shot and wait for the right moment to hit the shutter. It&#8217;s also pretty customisable, although I&#8217;ve just stuck with the basic exposure information and the grid to keep things clean. The electronic viewfinder (EVF) is also pretty decent, as far as these things go in today&#8217;s cameras, and you&#8217;ll need to flick over to it and activate &#8216;macro mode&#8217; if you want to shoot anything closer than 70cm/27in.</p>

<p><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/x100-strip-1100.jpg" alt="X100 w/ Gordy's strap, viewfinder and on tripod" /></p>

<p>It fits well in your hand, with just enough &#8220;bulk&#8221; on the right to give you a grip on it, and there&#8217;s quick access to ISO (via the customisable Function button on top), aperture (with the ring on front) and exposure compensation (small dial on top) so you don&#8217;t have to dig through menus. I find it equal to a DSLR in that respect—there&#8217;s no digging through menus for the major controls. I&#8217;ve set the RAW button to toggle the in-built 3-stop ND filter—which is great if you either a) don&#8217;t want to stop down too much, or b) run with your settings dialled in for indoor scenes and quickly want to keep the shutter from maxing out with a single button press.</p>

<p>Most important of all, of course, are the images the X100 produces. The dynamic range is great, and highlights roll off smoothly. It can be a tad &#8220;soft&#8221; wide open, but there&#8217;s nothing really wrong with that—it can add character to some images. Things also sharpen up as soon as you stop down (f/2.8 onwards). It does like to flare, but it&#8217;s not harsh—to me, I think a bit of flare is welcome. And then there&#8217;s the fantastic way it handles noise. It&#8217;s not noiseless, but the noise it does exhibit is pleasant and I rarely need to apply <em>any</em> NR to images below ISO 3200. If I&#8217;m shooting above that, the shot is usually a candidate for black-and-white anyway. I&#8217;m usually happy to set this thing to aperture priority, f/4, ISO 1000 and -1/3 EV and go out shooting in the mornings and afternoons without the need to worry about grainy images or dull colours.</p>

<p>It has its quirks, but most of the major ones have been addressed—including AF performance, write speed and interface responsiveness—through firmware updates, so if you&#8217;re reading circa-December 2011 reviews, put less weight on those points. The quirks that do still exist aren&#8217;t even close to being deal-breakers: the rear control wheel is a bit fiddly, as is the &#8220;Menu/OK&#8221; button, and the command toggle (below the shutter dial) doesn&#8217;t work the same (or at all) in all VF modes. The newer (and bigger) X-Pro 1 addresses those things however, so at least we know Fuji is learning from their mistakes. The AF is &#8220;GF1 grade&#8221; to me, which is to say it&#8217;s capable if you&#8217;re familiar with contrast-detect AF systems. I don&#8217;t miss shots due to the AF, but it&#8217;s also not a camera built for tracking objects/shooting sports—you&#8217;re looking at the wrong camera if you need that.</p>

<p>There&#8217;s also the mostly unanimous advice to use a 45MB/s SD card (or better) to keep shot-to-shot and image review speeds from being sluggish—I&#8217;m using a 16GB SanDisk Extreme (UHS-1), and don&#8217;t notice any particular issue there. I also bought two spare batteries and a wall+car charger (a <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B005CRHM5C/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=eatsleeprepea-20&amp;linkCode=as2">Wasabi Power kit from Amazon for USD$23</a>), although I find I get a decent number of shots out of the camera (with power saving mode off) as it is.</p>

<p>Overall, I couldn&#8217;t ask for much more from a camera. I don&#8217;t think it&#8217;s expensive—you&#8217;re basically getting the image quality of a prosumer DSLR with a great prime in a <em>much</em> more portable package—and its handling allows the camera to get out the way and let you get on with making photographs.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Instax]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/instax/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-03T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/instax</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Em&#8217;s Fuji Instax 210 (the wide format version) arrived today.</p>
<h3><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0276-Edit-1100.jpg" width="1500" /></h3> 
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lunch]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/lunch/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-29T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/lunch</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A late lunch at &#8221;<em>THAT Food Company</em>&#8220; in Bayswater (I recommend the &#8220;LOT&#8221; burger).</p>
<p><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0264-Edit-2-1100.jpg" width="1500" /><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0265-Edit-2-1100.jpg" width="1500" /><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0266-Edit-1100.jpg" width="1500" /></p> 
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Pines]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/the-pines/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-25T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/the-pines</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Landscaping.</p>
<p><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0230-Edit-1100.jpg" width="1500" /></p> 
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reaching]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/reaching/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-24T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/reaching</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In Fremantle, Perth.</p>
<h3><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/elithrar/7424425500/lightbox/" title="Flickr"><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0191-Edit-1100.jpg" width="1500" /></a></h3> 
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Lost]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/getting-lost/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-24T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/getting-lost</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Unsealed roads are the best ones.</p>
<p><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0218-Edit-1100.jpg" /><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0248-Edit-1100.jpg" /><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0249-Edit-1100.jpg" /><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0252-Edit-1100.jpg" /><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0254-Edit-1100.jpg" /></p> 
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Daytripping]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/daytripping/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-23T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/daytripping</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A morning well spent.</p>
<p><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0186-Edit-1100.jpg" width="1500" /></p>
<p><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0187-Edit-1100.jpg" width="1500" /></p>
<p><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0188-Edit-1100.jpg" width="1500" /></p>
<p><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0189-Edit-1100.jpg" width="1500" /></p>
<p><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0193-Edit-1100.jpg" width="1500" /></p>
<p><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0198-Edit-1100.jpg" width="1500" /></p> 
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doors]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/doors/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-21T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/doors</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>(from the bus)</p>
<p><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0183-Edit-1100.jpg" width="1500" /></p> 
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Commute]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/commute/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-20T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/commute</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>On the way to work.</p>
<p><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0173-Edit-1100.jpg" width="1500" /></p> 
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Runner]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/runner/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-19T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/runner</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hyde Park, Perth.</p>
<p><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0164-Edit-1100.jpg" width="1500" /></p> 
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Entrée]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/entr-e/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-16T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/entr-e</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Pre-dinner hot chocolate, macarons and photo-walks.</p>
<p><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0116-Edit-1100.jpg" width="1500" /><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0119-Edit-1100.jpg" /><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0115-Edit-1100.jpg" /></p> 
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breakfast]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/breakfast/"/>
    <updated>2012-06-15T00:00:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/breakfast</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>At Food for Me in Victoria Park, Perth. Their Eggs Benedict is fantastic: the hollandaise isn&#8217;t too sweet, the eggs are poached perfectly and their mango chutney is delectable—although I did forget to order them with smoked salmon. Em had the french toast w/ maple syrup, berries and bacon.</p>
<p><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0060-Edit-2-1100.jpg" width="1500" /><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0058-Edit-2-1100.jpg" width="1500" /><img height="996" src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0079-Edit-1100.jpg" width="1500" /></p> 
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
