<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Reviews | EATSLEEPREPEAT.NET]]></title>
  <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/categories/reviews/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/"/>
  <updated>2013-03-14T06:59:14+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Matt Silverlock]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[matt@eatsleeprepeat.net]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alien Skin Exposure vs. VSCO Film]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/alien-skin-exposure-vs-vsco-film/"/>
    <updated>2013-01-20T10:36:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/alien-skin-exposure-vs-vsco-film</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>During downtime or during periods where I've lacked a bit of motivation to go out and shoot, editing old photos and/or trying out some new post-processing techniques has often given me some inspiration to get out there again.</p>

<p>My process has always been fairly manual. Import into LR, fix any WB/exposure/highlight issues, apply a hand-crafted preset for some basic colour correction/vignetting/etc and then push the image into Photoshop + Alien Skin Exposure ("Exposure") and apply a film preset. I typically set my preferred presets as actions in PS so I can hit a couple of keyboard shortcuts and end up back in Lightroom with a neatly stacked TIFF image on top of the original RAW one. It's not the smoothest workflow, but the results are hard to beat.</p>

<p>Still, it's always worth shopping around on occasion to see what else is out there. I've always been impressed by a lot of photographers who use VSCO Film, and decided to dedicate my Sunday morning to comparing VSCO's film presets (VSCO 01 &amp; VSCO 02 for LR4) with Exposure's.</p>

<p>Note that I have historically used Fuji Astia (color; I love the real thing) and Kodak Tri-X (B+W; great grain) emulations for most of my shots, but have been leaning towards Fuji 400H (a great neutral film) and Ilford HP5 (finer grain than Tri-X). Exposure and VSCO Film both have these on offer, so I've compared their Pro 400H, HP5, Tri-X and Provia 160VC emulations. Images were edited beforehand w/ WB/tint set identically. Any obvious differences in hue are the results of the emulation only. Large (1920px) versions are available if you click through—you'll probably want to look at them if you want to examine the grain.</p>

<h4>Fuji 400H</h4>

<p>I've really taken a liking to 400H recently—so much so that I bought a few rolls of the real stuff today (in 35mm format) with a near-mint Minolta Hi-Matic 9 rangefinder. It has such great tones, and I've had problems pulling myself away from a couple of <a href="http://www.flickr.com/groups/1084764@N20/pool/">Flickr</a> <a href="http://www.flickr.com/search/groups/?w=481987%40N24&amp;m=pool&amp;q=400H">group</a> pools.</p>

<p><a href="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/ase_vs_vsco/ase_vsco_fuji_400h.jpg"><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/ase_vs_vsco/ase_vsco_fuji_400h_thumb.jpg" alt="Fuji 400H" /></a></p>

<p>Exposure definitely feels more vibrant here—the VSCO image has an odd tint to it.</p>

<hr />

<p><a href="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/ase_vs_vsco/ase_vsco_fuji_400h_2.jpg"><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/ase_vs_vsco/ase_vsco_fuji_400h_2_thumb.jpg" alt="Fuji 400H" /></a></p>

<p>This is a tough call. The VSCO image is slightly warmer (channeling some Portra, I feel) but Exposure's rendition is a little more "honest". The skin tones in Exposure's take are definitely more natural.</p>

<h4>Portra 160VC</h4>

<p>I've compared Portra 160VC as Exposure doesn't have a Portra 400 emulation, and it'd be remiss to not include Portra given its popularity.</p>

<p><a href="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/ase_vs_vsco/ase_vsco_portra_160vc.jpg"><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/ase_vs_vsco/ase_vsco_portra_160vc_thumb.jpg" alt="Portra 160VC" /></a></p>

<p>Big difference here. I feel the actual film <a href="http://www.flickr.com/groups/kodak_portra_160vc/pool/">lies somewhere in between</a>, as Exposure's take is much more saturated.</p>

<hr />

<p><a href="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/ase_vs_vsco/ase_vsco_portra_160vc_2.jpg"><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/ase_vs_vsco/ase_vsco_portra_160vc_2_thumb.jpg" alt="Portra 160VC" /></a></p>

<p>Exposure here, for sure. Looks more like Portra 160VC and has more "pop" to it.  The VSCO take isn't bad though, and there's no doubt plenty of people would prefer the less saturated take. I'm not huge on pushing saturation up, but I do like "enough".</p>

<h4>Ilford HP5</h4>

<p>I've always had a tough time deciding between HP5 and Tri-X. HP5 is a bit finer grained, but Tri-X has great blacks. Note that the "original" Tri-X (which these emulations feel like) isn't available anymore; Kodak changed the formula and re-branded it "400TX". The grain is a tad finer in the new stuff, but I digress.</p>

<p><a href="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/ase_vs_vsco/ase_vsco_ilford_hp5.jpg"><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/ase_vs_vsco/ase_vsco_ilford_hp5_thumb.jpg" alt="Ilford HP5" /></a></p>

<p>Tricky. VSCO is brighter, but the Exposure take has better blacks. I'd say that the Exposure image could probably do with a slight exposure push to compensate a little more. The VSCO image doesn't have nice grain (this is a problem with a number of their emulations; grain is very pattern-like).</p>

<hr />

<p><a href="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/ase_vs_vsco/ase_vsco_ilford_hp5_2.jpg"><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/ase_vs_vsco/ase_vsco_ilford_hp5_2_thumb.jpg" alt="Ilford HP5" /></a></p>

<p>I've compensated the Exposure shot a little—with a 10% opacity grey exclusion layer in PS—as VSCO gets to overwrite my own curve adjustments in Lightroom. It's not a totally fair comparison as a result, but it lifts the blacks and really helps show the detail. VSCO's black-and-white emulations are much flatter than real film, but this is also part of the attraction (and I like this look sometimes) for a lot of photographers. This could go either way, but I feel her eyes have more depth in Exposure's take and the grain (again) is more organic.</p>

<h4>Kodak Tri-X</h4>

<p>It's Tri-X. Most my black &amp; white work over the last six months uses this.</p>

<p><a href="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/ase_vs_vsco/ase_vsco_trix_400.jpg"><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2013/ase_vs_vsco/ase_vsco_trix_400_thumb.jpg" alt="Kodak Tri-X" /></a></p>

<p>Again, it's a tough call. <em>I</em> like the contrast in Exposure's Tri-X emulation, and I think it's much more like "<a href="http://www.flickr.com/groups/tri-x/pool/">the real thing</a>", but realism isn't always the goal. VSCO's grain here is actually (surprisingly) good for once, and I'd say it's the pick of the VSCO crop.</p>

<h4>Wrap-up</h4>

<p>Exposure's results are more pleasing to me, and in cases where I need to lift blacks or flatten things out I have more leeway to do so (that, and I'm already in Photoshop...). As aforementioned, it's Exposure's grain that really puts in ahead in my books: VSCO's grain "scans" are too static. Many of us use film emulations for the grain, and nailing that is important.</p>

<p>Both are about the same price: Exposure is <a href="https://app.alienskin.com/store/">$199</a> and VSCO Film is <a href="http://visualsupply.co/store">$119 per pack</a>. Film 02 has updated Portra presets; Film 01 has Pro 400H and Tri-X (I'd buy 01, personally). VSCO has a neat little preset "toolkit" for tinting shadows, highlights and making other minor tweaks, and ultimately is more friendly to use as a result. Exposure has a <em>lot</em> of other emulations (Kodachrome!), and offers a lot of choice (too much?) for those who want that.</p>

<p>It's a tough call. VSCO really makes your workflow easy: fix first, hit the preset and tweak if needed. Exposure is a bit clunkier and you end up with 100MB+ TIFFs eating up some space (even if space is cheap these days), although Lightroom automatic stacking makes this a minor issue overall. But Exposure's advantages—nicer grain, more natural saturation and more "pop" (however you quantify that)—outweigh the negatives.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuji X100 - Three Months In]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/fuji-x100-three-months-in/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-04T08:07:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/fuji-x100-three-months-in</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I've had the <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0043RS864/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=eatsleeprepea-20">X100</a> for three months now, and I feel it's time to add a few things to my <a href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/fuji-x100-review/">original review</a>. This review will be a little more technical than the first, but there (still) won't be any pixel peeping here.</p>

<p>First up: the RAW files. They're great, and there's a <em>lot</em> of latitude in them. I pushed a bunch of files from the <a href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/say-anything/">Say Anything</a> gig I went to—which I shot at ISO3200—a minimum of one stop and saw very little chroma (colour) noise. What noise there was had a great "film" look, and pushing the files around with my usual Lightroom + Photoshop + Alien Skin Exposure workflow didn't cause any problems. I'm still comfortably leaving the X100 set to ISO800/1000 on a daily basis (and using the ND filter to control shutter speed), without the need to worry about dull colours or ugly/distracting noise.</p>

<p>The battery life has been rock solid. There are some who seem to believe it has a sub-par battery life—and I guess if you're coming from an pro-grade DSLR, then it may seem bad in comparison—but it manages weeks on standby with a good handful of shots in-between. It also coped with four days away when I went to <a href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/yallingup/">Yallingup</a> in July—the spare batteries I brought down with me never saw any use (it was still near-full almost a week later). It might be the fact that I review sparingly and spend most of my time using the OVF that contributes to this—I'm not the kind to "spray and pray".</p>

<p>Reliability-wise, it hasn't locked up once. I've had firmware v1.30 on it since day zero, so that may have something to do with it, but I've never had to pop the battery out to reset the camera. It's almost managed to avoid any real dings or scratches, despite living sans-case in an inside pocket of my messenger bag. I have a JJC filter adapter ring and a <a href="http://www.bhphotovideo.com/c/product/622143-REG/B_W_66_042015_66_042015_49mm_Digital_Pro.html">silver B+W UV filter</a> on it; I don't use the hood as it adds too much depth. I not usually one to run with a UV filter on my cameras, but the X100 is the exception: it's an every-day, always-there tool, and any damage to the lens means the whole camera is out of action. I just made sure to buy a decent filter to minimise any added ghosting or flare, and so far I haven't had any problems.</p>

<p>The LCD could probably be a bit better (higher-res), and I have started to bump the AF mode dial on the front a bit more than I'd like. Part of that is attributed to the fact that it lives in my messenger bag (sans-case) and/or the cup-holder in my car, and therefore is outright more prone to being knocked. I've gotten used to the rear dial, but it's still a bit fiddly. Can't do much about that though—and it doesn't hugely impact the usability of the camera.</p>

<p>The <a href="http://www.gordyscamerastraps.com/neck-string-double/index.htm">Gordy's</a> strap (string; double attach; 50") that I picked up for it is still going strong, too. Matches the X100 well and is just long enough to sling bandolier-style over my body—but long enough that I can still pull the viewfinder up to my eye comfortably.</p>

<p>I'm still loving the OVF—even more as time goes on. I'm forever liking the frame-lines and what is effectively "greater than 100%" frame coverage. I do occasionally flick it over to the EVF if I really need to nail a composition—or shoot something close—but the other 90% of the time I'm using the OVF. It takes maybe a week to get used to the accuracy of the frame-lines vs. the distance of what you're shooting (and therefore your composition)—but after that it's smooth sailing.</p>

<p>The more time I spend with the X100 the more I know I made the right choice. There's no buyer's remorse here, despite considering the NEX-7 (unexciting RAW files; expensive with the 24mm), OM-D (too SLR-like), and the X-Pro 1 (just that bit too big). I can comfortably "see" in 35mm, which means I can almost frame a shot before lifting the camera to my eye. It's never intrusive at dinner tables, in the car, or over my shoulder on long walks. It rarely struggles in less-than-ideal lighting, excels in good light, and gives me the control I want; all of these things are exactly what I was after. It's almost a shame I waited so long to buy one.</p>

<p><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/DSCF0173-Edit-1100.jpg" alt="ISO 1000, f/2, 1/120s" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuji X100 Review]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/fuji-x100-review/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-08T12:54:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/fuji-x100-review</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>First up: this isn't a technical, pixel peeping review—it is however a review about the user experience, handling and image character. If that floats your boat, read on.</p>

<p>So: I bought a <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0043RS864/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=eatsleeprepea-20&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=390957&amp;creativeASIN=B0043RS864">Fuji X100</a> three weeks ago to replace my Panasonic GF1 + 20mm kit, which originally "replaced" my 5D Mark II + 35L. I was no longer worried about chasing paid work, and was instead just shooting street, editorial and landscapes for (mostly) myself. Having a camera that I could take <em>everywhere</em> (i.e. didn't need its own bag) was a huge driving factor in getting the GF1, even if overall image quality wasn't the same. It really didn't matter though, and I ended up taking a ton of great photos with it. It did have its quirks—average AF, dynamic range/RAW files, and no viewfinder—but those were trade-offs I was willing to make. When the X100 came out, I wasn't totally sold: I didn't really read up on it and my GF1 wasn't bugging me too much, so I keep shooting with what I had. But I kept running across amazing images from the X100, and the so-so RAW files from the GF1 (esp. compared with my old 5D2) were starting to grate just a little.</p>

<p>I sold my GF1 and lenses (I also had the 45mm f2.8 macro), waited for someone local to get stock, and bought the X100. And so far it's been outstanding.</p>

<p>The optical viewfinder (OVF), first of all, rocks. It's big, it's clear, and the best part about it is that it covers <em>beyond</em> the frame, allowing you to spot people just outside your shot and wait for the right moment to hit the shutter. It's also pretty customisable, although I've just stuck with the basic exposure information and the grid to keep things clean. The electronic viewfinder (EVF) is also pretty decent, as far as these things go in today's cameras, and you'll need to flick over to it and activate 'macro mode' if you want to shoot anything closer than 70cm/27in.</p>

<p><img src="http://static.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/x100-strip-1100.jpg" alt="X100 w/ Gordy's strap, viewfinder and on tripod" /></p>

<p>It fits well in your hand, with just enough "bulk" on the right to give you a grip on it, and there's quick access to ISO (via the customisable Function button on top), aperture (with the ring on front) and exposure compensation (small dial on top) so you don't have to dig through menus. I find it equal to a DSLR in that respect—there's no digging through menus for the major controls. I've set the RAW button to toggle the in-built 3-stop ND filter—which is great if you either a) don't want to stop down too much, or b) run with your settings dialled in for indoor scenes and quickly want to keep the shutter from maxing out with a single button press.</p>

<p>Most important of all, of course, are the images the X100 produces. The dynamic range is great, and highlights roll off smoothly. It can be a tad "soft" wide open, but there's nothing really wrong with that—it can add character to some images. Things also sharpen up as soon as you stop down (f/2.8 onwards). It does like to flare, but it's not harsh—to me, I think a bit of flare is welcome. And then there's the fantastic way it handles noise. It's not noiseless, but the noise it does exhibit is pleasant and I rarely need to apply <em>any</em> NR to images below ISO 3200. If I'm shooting above that, the shot is usually a candidate for black-and-white anyway. I'm usually happy to set this thing to aperture priority, f/4, ISO 1000 and -1/3 EV and go out shooting in the mornings and afternoons without the need to worry about grainy images or dull colours.</p>

<p>It has its quirks, but most of the major ones have been addressed—including AF performance, write speed and interface responsiveness—through firmware updates, so if you're reading circa-December 2011 reviews, put less weight on those points. The quirks that do still exist aren't even close to being deal-breakers: the rear control wheel is a bit fiddly, as is the "Menu/OK" button, and the command toggle (below the shutter dial) doesn't work the same (or at all) in all VF modes. The newer (and bigger) X-Pro 1 addresses those things however, so at least we know Fuji is learning from their mistakes. The AF is "GF1 grade" to me, which is to say it's capable if you're familiar with contrast-detect AF systems. I don't miss shots due to the AF, but it's also not a camera built for tracking objects/shooting sports—you're looking at the wrong camera if you need that.</p>

<p>There's also the mostly unanimous advice to use a 45MB/s SD card (or better) to keep shot-to-shot and image review speeds from being sluggish—I'm using a 16GB SanDisk Extreme (UHS-1), and don't notice any particular issue there. I also bought two spare batteries and a wall+car charger (a <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B005CRHM5C/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=eatsleeprepea-20&amp;linkCode=as2">Wasabi Power kit from Amazon for USD$23</a>), although I find I get a decent number of shots out of the camera (with power saving mode off) as it is.</p>

<p>Overall, I couldn't ask for much more from a camera. I don't think it's expensive—you're basically getting the image quality of a prosumer DSLR with a great prime in a <em>much</em> more portable package—and its handling allows the camera to get out the way and let you get on with making photographs.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
