<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Reviews | EATSLEEPREPEAT.NET]]></title>
  <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/categories/reviews/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/"/>
  <updated>2012-07-09T05:48:24+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Matt Silverlock]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[matt@eatsleeprepeat.net]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fuji X100 Review]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/fuji-x100-review/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-08T12:54:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.eatsleeprepeat.net/2012/fuji-x100-review</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>First up: this isn't a technical, pixel peeping review—it is however a review about the user experience, handling and image character. If that floats your boat, read on.</p>

<p>So: I bought a <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0043RS864/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=eatsleeprepea-20&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=390957&amp;creativeASIN=B0043RS864">Fuji X100</a> three weeks ago to replace my Panasonic GF1 + 20mm kit, which originally "replaced" my 5D Mark II + 35L. I was no longer worried about chasing paid work, and was instead just shooting street, editorial and landscapes for (mostly) myself. Having a camera that I could take <em>everywhere</em> (i.e. didn't need its own bag) was a huge driving factor in getting the GF1, even if overall image quality wasn't the same. It really didn't matter though, and I ended up taking a ton of great photos with it. It did have its quirks—average AF, dynamic range/RAW files, and no viewfinder—but those were trade-offs I was willing to make. When the X100 came out, I wasn't totally sold: I didn't really read up on it and my GF1 wasn't bugging me too much, so I keep shooting with what I had. But I kept running across amazing images from the X100, and the so-so RAW files from the GF1 (esp. compared with my old 5D2) were starting to grate just a little.</p>

<p>I sold my GF1 and lenses (I also had the 45mm f2.8 macro), waited for someone local to get stock, and bought the X100. And so far it's been outstanding.</p>

<p>The optical viewfinder (OVF), first of all, rocks. It's big, it's clear, and the best part about it is that it covers <em>beyond</em> the frame, allowing you to spot people just outside your shot and wait for the right moment to hit the shutter. It's also pretty customisable, although I've just stuck with the basic exposure information and the grid to keep things clean. The electronic viewfinder (EVF) is also pretty decent, as far as these things go in today's cameras, and you'll need to flick over to it and activate 'macro mode' if you want to shoot anything closer than 70cm/27in.</p>

<p><img src="http://f.cl.ly/items/3c421V210C342B1F3Y0c/x100-strip.jpg" alt="X100 w/ Gordy's strap, viewfinder and on tripod" /></p>

<p>It fits well in your hand, with just enough "bulk" on the right to give you a grip on it, and there's quick access to ISO (via the customisable Function button on top), aperture (with the ring on front) and exposure compensation (small dial on top) so you don't have to dig through menus. I find it equal to a DSLR in that respect—there's no digging through menus for the major controls. I've set the RAW button to toggle the in-built 3-stop ND filter—which is great if you either a) don't want to stop down too much, or b) run with your settings dialled in for indoor scenes and quickly want to keep the shutter from maxing out with a single button press.</p>

<p>Most important of all, of course, are the images the X100 produces. The dynamic range is great, and highlights roll off smoothly. It can be a tad "soft" wide open, but there's nothing really wrong with that—it can add character to some images. Things also sharpen up as soon as you stop down (f/2.8 onwards). It does like to flare, but it's not harsh—to me, I think a bit of flare is welcome. And then there's the fantastic way it handles noise. It's not noiseless, but the noise it does exhibit is pleasant and I rarely need to apply <em>any</em> NR to images below ISO 3200. If I'm shooting above that, the shot is usually a candidate for black-and-white anyway. I'm usually happy to set this thing to aperture priority, f/4, ISO 1000 and -1/3 EV and go out shooting in the mornings and afternoons without the need to worry about grainy images or dull colours.</p>

<p>It has its quirks, but most of the major ones have been addressed—including AF performance, write speed and interface responsiveness—through firmware updates, so if you're reading circa-December 2011 reviews, put less weight on those points. The quirks that do still exist aren't even close to being deal-breakers: the rear control wheel is a bit fiddly, as is the "Menu/OK" button, and the command toggle (below the shutter dial) doesn't work the same (or at all) in all VF modes. The newer (and bigger) X-Pro 1 addresses those things however, so at least we know Fuji is learning from their mistakes. The AF is "GF1 grade" to me, which is to say it's capable if you're familiar with contrast-detect AF systems. I don't miss shots due to the AF, but it's also not a camera built for tracking objects/shooting sports—you're looking at the wrong camera if you need that.</p>

<p>There's also the mostly unanimous advice to use a 45MB/s SD card (or better) to keep shot-to-shot and image review speeds from being sluggish—I'm using a 16GB SanDisk Extreme (UHS-1), and don't notice any particular issue there. I also bought two spare batteries and a wall+car charger (a <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B005CRHM5C/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=eatsleeprepea-20&amp;linkCode=as2">Wasabi Power kit from Amazon for USD$23</a>), although I find I get a decent number of shots out of the camera (with power saving mode off) as it is.</p>

<p>Overall, I couldn't ask for much more from a camera. I don't think it's expensive—you're basically getting the image quality of a prosumer DSLR with a great prime in a <em>much</em> more portable package—and its handling allows the camera to get out the way and let you get on with making photographs.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
